RONALD GUIDRY

Ahaliya Hashnia 21. Haifa, Israel. 3525538

0587847503

a ronaldguidry@hotmail.com

http://ronysweb.com/

https://github.com/Ronysweb

ABOUT ME

I was released from the army on December 2019. Made aliyah from Mexico in 2014.

I have a consistent work history, enjoy working in a team, supervisory experience, strong work ethic, strong interpersonal skills, strong initiative, team player, and hard worker.

SKILLS

- HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript, Bootstrap 4.
- Linux OS.
- Sales Representative working with CRM.
- WordPress, eCommerce, SEO.
- Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Publisher, Excel.

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Mother Tongue

English - Native Language

Hebrew - Good Level

Employment History

⊘Israel Defense Forces. 2017-2019.

Position: K-9 unit Air Force.

Duration: 2 years and 8 months.

Responsibilities:

- -Handling, training, and caring for personal dog.
- -Responding to emergency's alarms.
- -Interviewing suspects and witnesses.
- -Analyzing crime scenes and collecting evidence
- -Conducting searches and patrolling areas to search
- -Leading a team of soldiers
- Quality Leads Israel, Tel Aviv, Israel. 2014-2017.

Position: Sales representative and Customer service.

Duration: 3 years 8 months.

Responsibilities:

- -Acknowledging and resolving customer complaints.
- -Maintaining a positive, empathetic, and professional attitude.
- -Knowing our products inside and out.
- -Processing orders, forms, applications, and requests.
- -Training junior customer service representatives.
- -Responding promptly to customer inquiries.
- Factory Manufactures (Colecciones Sapir Sa de CV), Mexico City, Mexico. 2013-2014.

Position: Security Supervisor of storage and 135 employees.

Duration: 1 year.

Responsibilities:

- -Write and submit security reports
- -Provide security
- -Maintain law and order in area of jurisdiction
- -Monitor staff by patrolling with them
- -Assign work areas for officers to patrol
- -Protect the people and property
- -Conduct routine patrols with team
- -Look out for suspicious persons, vandalism or hazards
- -Respond to alarms and distress calls
- -Ensure all security systems, like the burglar alarms and CCTV are working properly

Education

Zero To Mastery Web Development 2016-2020 (Online Course)

Colegio Yavne Shio Y Anita Mondlak 2000-2012 (Mexico City, Mexico.)